SAADET ELİF TOKUOĞLU

İstanbul / Türkiye +90 53****** saadeteliftokuoglu@gmail.com

https://github.com/Saadet-T https://bugcrowd.com/LzzapS3c https://lzzaps3c.medium.com https://tryhackme.com/p/Lzzap https://www.linkedin.com/in/saad et-elif-tokuoğlu-ab2a59188/

SUMMARY

I began my career in cyber security at the age of 19 in 2020, joining Sparta Bilişim Teknolojileri Yazılım Danışmanlık Sanayi. After a while, I transitioned to RSU Bilişim ve Danışmanlık Hizmetleri Anonim Şirketi, initially as an intern and later took on a part-time role as a Cyber Security Consultant. I am someone who has experience in web application security and OSINT, and I enjoy creating practice environments to improve my skills in penetration testing.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Part-Time Cyber Security Consultant

RSU Bilişim ve Danışmanlık Hizmetleri A.Ş [09/2022 - 07/2023]

I took part in performing and reporting web application penetration tests. I was also responsible for the training and management of interns.

Intern

RSU Bilişim ve Danışmanlık Hizmetleri A.Ş. [06/2022 - 09/2022]

I had a training process where I learnt and practiced web application security and exploiting vulnerabilities.

Junior Penetration Tester

Sparta Bilişim Teknolojileri Yazılım Danışmanlık [11/2020 - 03/2021]

I was responsible for conducting and reporting web application penetration tests and preparing OSINT reports.

EDUCATION

University

SAKARYA ÜNİVERSİTESİ [2019 - 2023] -BİLGİSAYAR MÜHENDİSLİĞİ

SKILLS & PROFICIENCIES

- Web Application Penetration Testing (OWASP Methodologies)
- Open Source Intelligence Reporting
- Programming (Java, Python, C#)
- Tutoring
- Teamwork, multitasking, and attention to detail

LANGUAGES

English (Advanced)

TOOLS I'M FAMILIAR WITH

- Nmap
- Nessus
- Netsparker
- Acunetix
- GoPhish
- OWASP ZAP
- Metasploit
- Burp Suite
- SQLmap
- Gobuster
- APKTool
- Dex2jar etc.

SAADET ELİF TOKUOĞLU

CERTIFICATIONS & TRAINING

eJPT

[20/08/2023] eLearnSecurity

Offensive Siber Güvenlik

[18/08/2023] BÜSİBER

API Security Architect

[31/10/2022] API Academy

Pratical IoT Hacking

[06/2022]

Hacktrick

Practical Ethical Hacking

[06/02/2022]

TCM Security

Temel Ağ Teknolojileri

[02/07/2021]

BTK Akademi

Network Paket ve Protokol

Analizi

[24/09/2020] Bilişim Vadisi

PROJECTS

Tamper Playground (On-going(Currently Priva)

An exercise application prepared for learning and practising tamper script writing for SQLmap tool. Written in Java SpringBoot. https://github.com/Saadet-T/TamperPlayground

HYGIEA (Vulnerable Web Application)

As a graduation project, I developed a vulnerable web application with my friend. Our main goal in the project was to implement a reportable application that was closer to the vulnerabilities we saw in web application penetration tests, so we wanted to create a more realistic practice environment for people who try to enter the cyber security field by solving CTFs etc. We used PostgreSQL as database and Thymeleaf, SpringBoot for frontend and backend.

https://github.com/Saadet-T/Hygeia-1

403 Kangaroo (Burp Suite Extension)

It is an extension that aims to provide access to misconfigured pages, with adding certain headers and values to requests directed through Burp Suite. When you install the extension, the contents of the Headers.txt and Values.txt files are written to the directory where Burp Suite is located, with default values. If a user wants to add their own values or headers they can add them in the txt files . https://github.com/Saadet-T/403Kangaroo

403 Jumper & 403 jumper with multiple targets

The purpose of these tools is to bypass 403 forbidden returning pages. It basically brute-force certain bypass headers with localhost's address 127.0.0.1. Built with Python. https://github.com/Saadet-T/403-jumper-with-multiple-targets

Non Work Related Projects

Front-end testing with Selenium Software and Unit Testing with JUnit https://github.com/Saadet-T/YazilimTestiOdev-Junit https://github.com/Saadet-T/SeleniumOdev

https://github.com/Saadet-T/403Jumper/tree/main

REFERENCE

• It will be provided upon request